Hello friends, I am Karan Grover, I
welcome you all to Adi's YouTube channel for
stock brokers. Today's video
is special. In today's video, I will tell you
what credits do Tube Exports use before adding any stock to their portfolio.
This video will be
very useful for both experienced and beginners. So, please watch it till the end.
Friends, this video
is part 2 of our portfolio management. If you have already made it in part 1,
now to watch it,
you can see it by clicking on the link given in the description. You
can reset our page.
Today I will only tell you credits.
Check rate or with which you can shortlist any stock. The
first step to add it to your portfolio is the
share holding pattern of any company.
In Shivling Patan, the first
thing you have to see is whether the promoter holding is more than 50% or
less than 50%. Because the company is and if you
subscribe, the efforts to
increase the growth of the company kept increasing. This shows
that the
company's  Now let's talk about the fundamentals, that is,
how much money is invested by them or
how much their investment is increasing every quarter, the
ads that are there, their
support team Jyoti lists the details,
before investing in any stock,
their building is also very important
in any company, so with this
pancake appointment you
can click on any stock, now there is a
fear of the appointment of the last company, there will be a
problem,
subscribe before buying all these things because
when
kids can face any company like cost
reaction, any company is a student,
hence subscribe to my channel
and their pension has been stopped that
any company which has free money can
launch itself in the market,
can subscribe, friends, I had
decided its name is John, subscribe to this company
from its last quarter five
and very good,
okay, in that company, I have to choose such a company
which is
a good investment in our future portfolio,
friends, which is fourth reddy, any company
you choose, the companies of that sector have
its market  We should
talk about the computing company we appointed, for example, let's
talk about the company, the company
must have heard every month,
subscribe, click on the company, it is a
very good company with market share,
subscribe, subscribe, the
official teaser is a leading company among the companies,
that person is fit, so we should include some such companies
in our portfolio, for a
future career, it has relative, what is it, we
need top performers, they should be
top performers of their segment, there should be no decrease in the performance of the company in the last 10 years, 20
years,
as soon as the
companies get listed in the Indian stock market,
now their performance keeps increasing,
subscribe, the advantage of that company is
that this company has a lot of experience,
now they can reduce the uncertainty over it,
friends, subscribe,
before that I would like to tell you some
more secrets, I have made some experts of portfolio
management, so
definitely watch that video, the link is given
in the description, and if you still have
n't liked the video, then please like the video
or its huge problem will end now  I am going to
tell you in this video only
that any
industry, any company should keep any appointment, whether the
government policies will fulfill this time
or not, like the Servi
budget, the physical policy will be discussed in the middle of the comment, then there will be
changes in the policies, subscribe the video of which I also
made a video, so please subscribe related to this, it is
positive for all the companies related to the agriculture sector, it will give a
positive impact in one feature, the budget
came and it came for resources, the
companies which make Saurabh channel or those whose
work is
Renu Resources, that
budget was also positive for the gas sector, so we have to keep those companies in
mind, we should include it in our portfolio,
like
they had released a good budget for the gas sector, so Idea
company subscribe, so you have given the
subscribe button, friends,
please subscribe to my channel,
because it will
help you in building a quantum portfolio and when you
invest, you will get a multibagger, so
please subscribe, you
can put any question in the comment section  Thank you